I mentioned a couple words while I
was describing these different kinds
我在描述不同种类的基金时
of funds that I wanted to
touch on real quickly.
提到了一些词语
I said liquid a couple times.
我提到 liquid 许多次
What that means is the ease
with which one can buy or
它的意思是
sell shares in a particular holding.
一个人可以买卖特定所有物的股份的难易程度
Stocks are extremely liquid.
股票是极其的 liquid
ETFs are liquid in the same way,
in other words
ETFs 同样也是 liquid 换句话说
you can go to a stock exchange,
you can buy an ETF and sell an ETF.
你可以去一个股票交易所 你可以买卖 ETF
It's priced just like a stock,
but when you buy it,
它的价格就像股票一样 但是当你买的时候
you're buying shares of multiple
stocks instead of just a single stock.
你是在买多支股票 而不仅仅是一支
But ETFs are liquid because
they're easy to trade.
但是 ETFs 是 liquid 因为它们交易起来很容易
They're also liquid in many
cases because there's so
它们在多种情况下都是 liquid
much dollar value trading
in them each day.
因为每天都有许多美元价值交易
If you look up an ETF on
say Google Finance or
如果你在 Google Finance 或 Yahoo Finance 上搜索一个 ETF
Yahoo Finance, you can see how
much volume is traded each day.
你可以看到每天的交易量有多少
And ETFs with higher volumes
are even more liquid.
有更高交易量的 ETF 也就更 liquid
I mentioned large cap.
我提到了很多 cap
What cap means here is capitalization or
in other words,
cap 在这里的意思是资本总额 换句话说
how much is the company
worth according to
公司的价值多少是依据
number of shares that are outstanding,
times the price of the stock.
股份的数量 乘以 股票的价格
So, some really huge cap stocks,
因此 一些真正的大资本总额股票
say like Apple are worth many,
many billions of dollars.
比如 苹果公司 价值大量的美元
So when I say large cap stocks,
that's what I'm referring to.
当我提到大资本总额股票时 那就是我所指的
There's also small cap stocks that
are similarly, have lower value.
也有一些小资本总额的股票 它们有更低的价值
And one thing to mention as long as
we're on this topic, is the price of
需要提到一个关于这个话题的东西是
a stock really only relates to
what one share is selling at.
股票的价格只和股份的售出价格有关
It doesn't relate to the overall
value of the company.
和公司的总价值无关
We'll get into all of these
topics a little bit later.
我们后面会深入了解这些概念
Now to recap, there are at least
these three types of funds.
扼要重述 有这三种类型的基金
There are electronically traded funds,
它们是电子交易的基金
which you can trade like
stocks on a stock market.
你可以在股票交易市场像交易股票一样交易它们
There's mutual funds, that
are a little bit harder to get in and
共同基金更难进入和退出
out of, but
you can trade them on a daily basis.
但你可以每天交易
You usually have to go
through a specific broker.
你通常需要通过一个特别的经纪人
You can't just trade them on your own,
and
你不可能自己交易这些基金
finally hedge funds require a specific
agreement to trade into or out of.
最后 对冲基金要求一个关于进入和退出的特别协议
Okay, those are the three
major types of funds.
好的 这就是三种主要类型的基金